The greatest treasure lies within.
Lost & Found is a adventure, family, mystery film directed by Joseph Itaya.
Sent to spend the summer with their uncle on a remote island, young brothers Andy and Mark learn that their eccentric
grandfather once owned the island, but vanished without a trace…taking with him the secret to a vast fortune.
Delving into the mysterious past of the island, the brothers discover that their grandfather designed a complex treasure
hunt, a hunt that could lead to unimaginable wealth and heal their broken family – if they can find it in time.
Sinister forces also search for the money and will stop at
nothing to keep the boys from their quest.
As the adventure unfolds, the boys learn that the bonds of family are the most valuable
riches of all, and that some family secrets can’t stay buried forever.
Andy Walton, played by Justin Kelly.
Mark Walton, played by Benjamin Stockham.
Trent Walton, played by Jason Patric.
John Broman, played by Cary Elwes.
Jim Walton, played by Greg Bryk.
Sally Walton, played by Kim Selby.
Lost & Found is a 2016 mystery adventure film directed by Joseph Itaya and
starring Justin Kelly, Benjamin Stockham, Cary Elwes and Jason Patric.
The film explores themes of treasure, island,
underground, treasure hunt, summer.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.